To borrow Tendou's words for a second...
（牛島(うしじま)若利(わかとし)）
天童(てんどう)の言葉を借りると
I'm starting to get into it!
（牛島）ノてきた
（山口(やまぐち)忠(ただし)）あ
There's something wrong with his hand.
（影山(かげやま)飛雄(とびお)）アイツ手変です
（菅原(すがわら)孝支(こうし)）
勝負に出なきゃ勝利もない
But you have to risk something if you want a reward!
Fly
Karasuno is only Karasuno when we're persistently attacking!
執ように攻めてこそ烏野(からすの)
Full-team synchronized attack!
（烏野一同）
シンクロ攻撃オル
Karasuno                  Shiratorizawa
All right!
（白鳥沢(しらとりざわ)一同）
しゃ
Episode Eight:
An Annoying Guy
（横山(よこやま)静康(しずやす)）
ああチクショ
Damn it!
See? That's why you've gotta have
someone stay back to dig out a block.
（男性）もうほらやぱ
ブロクフォロしないと
Having everyone attack is way too reckless!
（男性）全員攻撃なんて
ムチャなんだて
That block was rather effective.
（及川(おいかわ)徹(とおる)）
今のブロクは相当効いたね
Did that just decide this match?
（岩泉(いわいずみ)一(はじめ)）これで決またか
（菅原）次も
We'll...
We'll do that again next time.
（菅原）次もやるから
（ホイスル）
Shiratorizawa!
（鳥養(うかい)繋心(けいしん)）日向(ひなた)ブロクの
タイミングは常に意識しろ
Hinata.
Shiratorizawa!
Always keep the block timing in your head.
Since you're short, that'll be much more important for you.
お前にはタパがない分—
Shiratorizawa!
他の連中より重要になる
（日向(ひなた)翔陽(しょうよう)）うん
Right.
Shiratorizawa!
If you feel like you're going to be even
a little late, switch over to a soft block.
（繋心）ほんのちょとでも
遅れたと感じたら—
すかさずソフトブロクに
切り替えだ
Shiratorizawa!
皿すね
The plate, right?
Push through!
（ホイスル）
All right!
（烏野一同）よしゃ
Sorry.
（牛島）すまん
（五色(ごしき)工(つとむ)）ドンマイです
Shake it off!
Shiratorizawa                 Karasuno
（田中(たなか)冴子(さえこ)）
ハァやと切れた
They finally stopped him.
How many points in a row did they get with Ushiwaka serving there?
（嶋田(しまだ)誠(まこと)）今のウシワカの
サブのタンで—
何連続得点だ
Five?
（滝ノ上(たきのうえ)祐輔(ゆうすけ)）６点だな
Six.
３分の１以上かよ
That's more than a third of what they need to win!
Hinata's coming back out now, though.
でもここから日向の出番だ
Pull something off again!
また何かやてくれ
（日向）よしゃ
Yeah!
成田(なりた)さん１本ナイサ
Give us a good serve, Narita!
Give us a good one!
（田中(たなか)龍之介(りゅうのすけ)）ナイサ
（成田(なりた)一仁(かずひと)）フゥ
（ホイスル）
いくぞう
Here I go!
(れおん)）う
すまん
Sorry!
Tendou!
（牛島）天童
（天童(てんどう)覚(さとり)）ほお
（田中）旭(あさひ)さん
Asahi!
（東峰(あずまね)旭(あさひ)）はあ
（日向）うあ
It's not Kageyama setting. I need to wait to jump!
（日向）
影山じゃない飛び出すな
But I can do first tempo with anyone!
誰とでもファストテンポ
（天童･日向）のわ
（田中）ブロク１枚
One blocker!
（ホイスル）
（田中）おしゃ
All right!
Go, go, Karasuno!
（応援団）いけいけ烏野
（菅原･田中）うおい
We're just two points behind!
Shiratorizawa                 Karasuno
（菅原）２点差だ
Is your eye okay, Hinata?
（田中）日向目大丈夫か
うううす
Yep!
You sure got hit in a strange place.
変なとこで受けたな
My hands couldn't get up in time,
so I thought about receiving it with my face,
（日向）手が間に合わなくて
顔面レシブだて思たけど—
but I didn't want it to hit my nose either.
鼻に当たたらイヤだから
What?!
（菅原）えじゃあ
見えててずらしたのかよ
So you turned your face because you could see it coming?
Well, if I got a nosebleed, I'd have to go back to the bench.
（日向）鼻血が出たら
ベンチ下げられるから
（田中･菅原）あハハ
（牛島）烏野１年コンビの
ウワサを聞いた時
After I heard about Karasuno's first-year duo,
そして学校で俺のボルを
奪た時—
and then when he stole my ball at school,
I had high hopes.
俺は期待した
今まで出会た—
I hoped he was like the other small
yet talented players I've met.
小柄で優れた選手たちのような
存在なんだろうと
But I was wrong.
だが違た
I couldn't feel the same polished skills or intelligence in him.
そんな選手たちのような
優れた技巧も知性も感じない
But...
なるほど
I see.
Something about him annoys me.
何かがイヤだ
I haven't once doubted that we would win.
俺は俺たちが勝つことを
疑わない
But right now, I'm completely sure...
でも今初めて明確に—
that I want to crush you.
お前をたたきつぶしたい
（日向）は
く
（菅原）ん
（ホイスル）
Give us a good serve, Kazuhito!
よしよしいいぞ諦めんなよ
All right, keep it up.
Don't give up!
ななああれ
Oh, hey, look!
Kageyama's warming up!
影山がアプしてる
He's going back in!
戻てくるぞ
Oohira!
（白布(しらぶ)賢二郎(けんじろう)）大平さん
（大平）て
（ホイスル）
（白鳥沢一同）
うしゃ
All right!
Shiratorizawa                  Karasuno
（日向）口の中血の味
I can taste blood in my mouth.
I wonder if Shouyou's in pain after all.
（冴子）
翔陽やぱり痛いのかな
でもブロクフォロ
Though having someone there
to dig out a block is reassuring, isn't it?
いてくれると心強いね
Earlier, he stayed back because only
Azumane could've realistically spiked it,
（嶋田）さきはもう—
東峰が打つしかないて
分かてたから—
フォロに入てたけど
基本烏野は入れるヤツは
全員攻撃に入れてスタイル
but normally, Karasuno has everyone who can attack go for it.
They don't think about getting blocked. They trust that they won't.
捕また時より
どう捕まらないかて考え方
So as soon as they get blocked, they're basically done for.
だから捕また時点で
ほぼアウト
昔はブロクフォロ
ちゃんと入れて—
Though we did get yelled at about staying back
to dig out a block quite a bit back in the day.
よく怒られてたけどな
If I were the coach, I'd do the same thing.
俺が監督でも言うわ
Actually, even as a player, I can't help but
hope that someone digs out a blocked ball.
いや選手としても—
フォロ入てくれよて
思ちゃうよ
It's scary otherwise.
だて怖(こえ)えもん
（牛島）ふ
Yes! Good job, Wakatoshi!
（瀬見(せみ)英太(えいた)）よしよし若利ナイス
（白布）五色
Goshiki!
Block the cross-court spike...
（菅原）クロスをしめる
and have Daichi in the path of a straight spike!
ストレトには大地(だいち)がいる
Bring it on!
（五色）上等ストレト勝負
I'm gonna take my chance with a straight spike!
（澤村(さわむら)大地(だいち)）う
すまん長い
Sorry! It went long!
Suga!
スガ
（菅原）う
（菅原）ここである程度の
安全を選んだら—
If we go for what's safe right now, it'll mean we never changed!
昔のままなんだよ
またやる気だ
They're going to do it again!
Aren't they scared it'll fail?
ビビんねえのかよ
Full-team synchronized attack!
（烏野一同）
シンクロ攻撃オル
（天童）フォム的には
バクトスて感じじゃない
Judging by his form, he won't do a backward set.
I haven't seen him do any combo attacks with number ten.
10番とのコンビは
一度も見てない
となると後ろのヒゲいや
So it'll probably go to the guy with the beard in the back...
No.
（菅原）次もやるから
We'll do that again next time.
（日向）えい
（菅原）ふ
（田中）でい
（ホイスル）
（天童）分かている
I know.
If I'm going through this thought process, I've already lost.
こういう思考に陥た時点で
俺は負けている
"Is there a set coming for me?"
（菅原）
“俺にトスは上がるのか”
I'm not going to think about that.
そんなこと考えない
"I'm just going to hit it."
Boo-yah, boo-yah, boo-yah!
“俺が打つのだ”
そう思て突込むことが—
By going to attack with that in mind,
the opposing blockers become confused.
どれだけ
相手ブロクを惑わすのか
Boo-yah!
（日向）ソイ
It's obvious when you see their faces.
（菅原）
こいつらを見てたら分かる
I can't believe Sugawara was able to fearlessly
charge in like that after being shut down last time!
よくあのどシャトのあと—
怖がらずに
突込んで来れたな菅原
I'm sure he's scared, but I guess it's important to have
a strong determination to attack to overpower the fear.
怖いんだろうけど—
それ以上に攻撃の意思を
持つことが大事てことだ
Satori!
（鷲匠(わしじょう)鍛治(たんじ)）覚
（天童）い
（鷲匠）手出せコラ
Stick your hands up, damn it!
I don't care if your prediction ends up wrong!
読みが外れてもいい
そんなもん
百も承知で入れてんだ
I put you in there knowing damn well that might be a possibility!
Yessir.
（天童）ういす
来た来た
（嶋田･冴子）おお
（ブザ
Here he comes!
Are you finally back, Tiredpants?
バテ山(やま)君は
やと復活ですか
Watch the back of your head.
（影山）
後頭部に気をつけろよ
（日向）うう
（ホイスル）
Give us a good serve, Kageyama!
（澤村）影山１本ナイサ
（影山）う
（山形(やまがた)隼人(はやと)）う
He's able to serve like that right after subbing back in?!
（山形）復活して
すぐこのサブかよ
（西谷(にしのや)夕(ゆう)）帰てくる
It's coming back!
チャンスボルだ丁寧に
You can score here! Watch out for...
Got i—
オライ
（影山）オライ
Got it!
（白布）ファストタチが
そのままセト
He's setting it straight away?
（天童）クソが
Damn!
（ホイスル）
There it is! The straight-down hit!
（男性）出た真下打ち
I-I didn't really see it, but everything's so fast!
（男性）
よよく分かんねえけど—
全部速(はえ)えよ
They're just one point behind!
Shiratorizawa                 Karasuno
（男性）１点差だ
Now I really don't know who's going to win!
（男性）分かんなく
なてきた
（影山）
こいつ俺はいつもの速攻で—
That bastard!
Great job, Hinata!
I thought that our usual fast attack would've been enough of a surprise, but this time he came at me on purpose!
That was awesome!
十分奇襲になると思てたのに
Thanks!
今回は
わざと突込んできやがた
危ねえだろうが
That's really dangerous, you dumbass!
Go, go!
（教頭）いけいけ
出し足(た)んねえぞ
Hey! You guys aren't being loud enough!
援）
You can do it!
Ushijima!
Be Courageous Warriors
Shiratorizawa                 Karasuno
Now they're in the double digits.
（滝ノ上）向こう
フタ桁乗たか
（ブザ
Focus on one point at a time!
His serves are intense.
（菅原）サブ強烈だぞ
１本で切てくれ
You can't let him get going!
（男子生徒）
なあ何で正セタ—
Hey, why isn't Semi our starting setter?
瀬見さんじゃないのかな
He's way better than Shirabu, to be honest.
ぶちゃけ白布さんより
うまいだろ
It all depends on what you consider to be better.
（男子生徒）
うまさの基準にもよるべよ
俺は白布さんも
安全な感じで好きだけど
I think Shirabu's pretty reliable, so I prefer him.
（瀬見）俺の何が白布に
劣ているのかは分かている
I know what makes me inferior to Shirabu.
It's the need to show just how good I am.
自分の力を誇示したいという
欲求が強いこと
Even though I know our setter doesn't
need that right now, I can't stop it.
それが今の白鳥沢のセタに
不要だと分かていても—
止められないんだ
（ホイスル）
（瀬見）でもサブは
サブだけは自由
But I'm free to go all-out with my serves!
（瀬見）ふどあ
（西谷･田中）あああ
（ホイスル）
A service ace!
ノタチエス
（瀬見）よしゃ
All right!
（応援団員）ナイスキ瀬見
Nice serve, Semi!
Be Courageous Warriors
（ブザ
Shiratorizawa                 Karasuno
Semi!
I have to find the right words to say to them.
（繋心）何か
何かこいつらにかける言葉を
Shiratorizawa!
（応援団）白鳥沢白鳥沢
白鳥沢
Shiratorizawa!
（滝ノ上）う
（嶋田）く
（冴子）黙るな
Don't shut up!
Shiratorizawa!
This is exactly when we should be cheering!
こういう時こそ応援でしょうが
Shiratorizawa!
We're going to finish this.
一気に決めるぞ
（瀬見）おう
Yeah.
Eita, hit another serve like—
英太君もう１本ん
（烏野応援団）
燃えろ燃えろ烏野
Fire it up, fire it up, Karasuno! Get it, get it, Karasuno!
（烏野応援団）決めろ決めろ烏野
燃えろ燃えろ烏野
決めろ決めろ烏野
（冴子･嶋田･滝ノ上）
燃えろ燃えろ烏野
決めろ決めろ烏野
（一同）燃えろ燃えろ烏野
（教頭）いけいけ烏野
（応援団）燃えろ燃えろ烏野
決めろ決めろ烏野
燃えろ燃えろ烏野
Below lies the City of Trees, Sendai!
（白鳥沢応援団）杜(もり)のみやこ
真下に押さえ
And when you look up, the magnificent Sendai Castle!
Be Courageous Warriors
あおげば雄々(おお)し
仙台(せんだい)城
われらの学び舎(や)
Fire it up, fire it up, Karasuno! Get it, get it, Karasuno!
Our school, our glorious Shiratorizawa Academy!
烏野決めろ決めろ烏野
燃えろ燃え
Fire it up...
われらの学び舎(や)
（ブザ
（白鳥沢応援団）
ああ栄光の—
白鳥沢学園
（ホイスル）
Our glorious Shiratorizawa Academy!
（天童）英太君
もう１本ナイサ
Give us an other good serve, Eita!
（瀬見）ぐ
Here's our chance to score!
（大平）チャンスボル
（田中）うぐ
（日向）く
（瀬見）若利
Wakatoshi!
（日向）う
（牛島）な
（影山）
ネトからあんなに離れて
That far from the net?!
（五色）く
（ホイスル）
（一同）おしゃ
All right!
He stopped it!
（嶋田）止めた
（冴子）翔陽
Shouyou!
（武田(たけだ)一鉄(いてつ)）ナナイスブロク
N-Nice blo—
Was that a block?
今のはブロク
I told him to do a soft block, but that was more like an insanely close receive than a block.
ソフトブロクとは
言たけども—
あれはもはやブロクではなく
超至近距離レシブだな
あんなの顔面が怖くて
できねえわ
I'd be too scared of that hitting my face to ever do that!
（牛島）くう
Now Karasuno's in the double digits too!
Shiratorizawa                  Karasuno
（冴子）烏野も
フタ桁乗た
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Haikyuu
!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Haikyuu
!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Haikyuu
!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Haikyuu
!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Haikyuu
!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Haikyuu
!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Haikyuu
!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Haikyuu
!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Haikyuu
!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Haikyuu
!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Haikyuu
!!
Karasuno High School vs Shiratorizawa Academy
Haikyuu
!!
Shiratorizawa                 Karasuno
（冴子）烏野も
フタ桁乗た
Now Karasuno's in the double digits too!
（日向）よしよしゃしゃ
Yes! All right! Yeah!
Don't get so worked up over a lucky shot!
まぐれで
舞い上がてんじゃねえ
That was a block that got in the way of a receive.
レシブの邪魔になるブロクだぞ
U-Ushijima, you just got stopped by a nameless first-year.
（五色）う牛島さん
無名の１年に止められるなんて
まだまだですね
Guess you've still got a ways to go.
I guess so.
そうだな
（五色）う
Ushijima is a great ace
that always has people covering him.
（五色）牛島さんは常に
マクされる大エス
It's no surprise that his spikes get stopped sometimes.
止められることだて当然ある
But getting blocked by such a tiny first-year is different.
でもあんな小さな１年が
Hinata, you're serving next.
Right!
He actually had the instinct to jump back at that moment...
（斉藤(さいとう)明(あきら)）
あそこで後ろに跳ぶセンス
（ブザ
（鷲匠）うう
Yeah!
（西谷･成田）しゃ
フゥ
（影山）成田さん
Narita, go in for a spike whenever you like.
I'll sync up with your timing.
いいように入てきてください
合わせます
R-Right.
おおう
（ブザ
行てこい
Get out there!
（ブザ
We're counting on you!
頼むぞ
（一同）山口いけ
Go, Yamaguchi!
Don't hold back.
（澤村）畳みかけろ
（山口）あ
There's not a single thing for you to be scared of.
ビビることなんか１個もねえ
I'll be aiming to hit it diagonally right at Ushiwaka,
（山口）狙いはウシワカの
対角線上へますぐ
but there's no point if I don't hit it hard too.
でも緩いボルじゃ意味はない
（ホイスル）
（山口）だ
Hayato!
（大平）隼人
（山形）クソ
Damn it!
We can score here!
（田中）チャンスボル
（山口）はい
Got it!
Here we go!
（澤村）いくぞ
Synchronized attack!
（烏野一同）シンクロ攻撃
Come here!
（五色）来いこちに来い
Come right over here!
（澤村）う
（ホイスル）
All rig—
やえく
Shiratorizawa                 Karasuno
Yes!
（烏野一同）
よしゃ
He touched the net?! Talk about lucky!
タチネトラキ
I think there's more to it than just luck!
だけじゃないと思う
（冴子）ん
If we keep hitting them hard,
they're going to start pushing back.
（鳥養(うかい)一繋(いけい)）
こちが強い力で押せば—
相手も押し返したくなるもんだ
（五色）クソ
Damn it...
（ホイスル）
It's all yours!
（山形）頼む
（五色）えい
（山形）う若利
Wakatoshi!
Wait! Take it slow!
ゆくりだゆくり
Ready, and... jump!
Despite all these barriers we've put up, it's still not enough to stop him?!
（東峰）これだけ打ちづらい
条件そろても—
止まんねえのかよ
Got it!
（田中）オライ
（影山）う
（成田）く
We didn't sync up!
（成田）合わない
（白布）う
（ホイスル）
（一同）うおお
（田中）よしゃ
追いついた
All right! We tied it up!
Shiratorizawa                 Karasuno
高かたすね修正します
That was a little high. I'll correct it for next time.
No, uh... Sure.
（成田）いやあうん
This is your first time working together, yet you went for a fast attack?!
（白布）
今日初めて合わせる速攻を—
ここで使うのかよ
（東峰）山口もう１本
Do it again, Yamaguchi!
（ホイスル）
（山口）て
（山口）長い
Did I hit it too far?
Let it go!
（山形）アウト
（五色）あ
（ホイスル）
All right!
Sorry. I waited too long to make a call.
（山形）
すまんジャジ遅かた
No, uh...
いえあのクソ
Damn it!
Yamaguchi!
（烏野一同）山口
Nice serve, Yamaguchi!
（澤村）ナイスだ山口
（山口）あざす
Thanks!
タイ
（牛島）どうした五色
Time—
What's the matter, Goshiki?
Shiratorizawa!
Why would you have any reason
to panic with all of your talent?
お前のその実力で
何を焦る必要があるんだ
Shiratorizawa!
（山形･大平）あ
（鷲匠）ふん
Shiratorizawa!
You're right.
We'll stop it next time.
He doesn't dress up his words, nor are they ambiguous.
（大平）飾らず
何の含みも他意もない
Right!
There's no encouragement—only the truth.
Shiratorizawa!
鼓舞ではなく事実
大エスからエスへ—
No more words need to be said
from the great ace to the ace.
これ以上の言葉はない
They turned it around!
Shiratorizawa                 Karasuno
（男性）ひくり返した
３連続得点
That's three points in a row!
Holy crap!
（男性）おいおいヤベえぞ
They might just win this thing!
マジでこのまま
いちまうんじゃねえか
Win!
勝て勝て烏野
Win, Karasuno!
（ホイスル）
All right!
（山口）よしあ
（大平）ふ
That's perfect, Oohira.
（白布）完璧です大平さん
（白布）ぐ
（五色）ふ
（ホイスル）
（白鳥沢一同）しゃ
All right!
Whoa. That angle was brutal.
うわ角度えげつな
He precisely hit it through the incomplete block.
的確に未完成なブロクの上を
Goshiki!
（ブザ
I'm sure he wanted to make up for his last serve receive.
本人はサブレシブで
挽回(ばんかい)したかたでしょうけどね
Great job, Yamaguchi.
山口よくやたあとは任せろ
Leave the rest to me!
But you're going to be switching
with Nishinoya immediately.
あでも西谷さんと
すぐ交代じゃん
Tsutomu, keep calm!
工落ち着けよ
（五色）分かてます
I know!
（ホイスル）
いくぞ
Let's do this!
（３人）さ来い
Bring it!
（五色）ふ
Damn it!
チクショが
Isn't number eight supposed to be the impulsive type?!
（滝ノ上）あの８番
直情タイプじゃねえのかよ
Tsutomu is the only first-year in our starting lineup.
工はうちで唯一の
１年スタメンだナメんなよ
Don't underestimate him.
（西谷）ああ
（田中）ノヤさん
Noya!
（ホイスル）
All right!
（白鳥沢一同）しゃ
Shiratorizawa                  Karasuno
Nice spike, Ushijima!
追い詰められたな烏野
They've got Karasuno cornered.
Ushijima!
Four-eyes isn't here, either.
しかもメガネ君もいないからね
I wonder how they're gonna survive this match point.
One more point! One more point!
このマチポイントを
どうやてしのぐか
（ホイスル）
（五色）ふん
Nice receive!
（３人）ナイスレシブ
Synchronized attack!
（烏野一同）シンクロ攻撃
（影山）ふ
（澤村）う
（ホイスル）
All right!
You actually made the guy
who just received the ball spike it?
（川西(かわにし)太一(たいち)）あえてレシブ直後の
ヤツに打たすのかよ
Shiratorizawa                 Karasuno
（斉藤）デュス
It's a deuce.
そろそろスタミナも
限界のはずなのに—
They should be running out of stamina by now, yet they're all still able to run around like that.
まだ全員で助走に入るのか
Toying with us using superior numbers...
数での翻弄(ほんろう)
確かに有力な攻撃と
認めざるを得ねえな
I have no choice but to admit
that it's an effective method of attack.
Coach!
（鷲匠）監督
（鷲匠）レシブは
誰にも負けませんし—
I won't lose to anyone when it comes to receiving, and
I can jump really high, so I'm confident in my attacks too!
自分はジャンプ力もあるので
攻撃にも自信があります
Right.
（監督）ああそれで
もう少し高さがあればなあ
Now you just have to get a bit taller.
I'm so small that I can't even fight?
（鷲匠）俺は小さいから
戦うことすらできないのか
I'm going to lose to someone just because they're tall?
ただ大きいだけのヤツに
負けるのか
One more!
（部員）もう１本
One more, please!
（部員）もう１本お願いします
No one here is "just" tall.
（鷲匠）ここにはただ
大きいだけのヤツなんていない
I understand that.
分かてるんだそんなことは
I envy them, and they annoy me,
妬(ねた)ましくいまいましく
強烈に憧れる
yet I admire them greatly.
（部員）う
Do I want a way to fight in spite of my short stature?
（鷲匠）俺は小さくても
戦えるすべが欲しいのか
No, I...
違う俺は
（滝ノ上）ブレイクしなきゃ
烏野の崖ぷちは変わらない
If they can't score twice in a row,
Karasuno's going to keep being in danger.
Their stamina and concentration
could run out at any moment.
もう体力も集中も切れる寸前
They just need to get the ball up in the air after Shiratorizawa's cannon spikes it any way they can!
とにかく白鳥沢の強烈な
大砲１発を—
どんな形でも上げてくれ
Give us a good serve, Daichi!
（繋心）く
（澤村）う
It's not gonna make it!
（滝ノ上･嶋田）短い
（大平）うう
（大平）ネト際狙うにも
程があるだろ
There has to be a limit for how
close you can hit it to the net!
Goshiki!
（牛島）五色
（五色）はい
Right!
（田中）く
Keep the rally going!
つながてるつながてるよ
The last hit is all yours, Kageyama!
（東峰）影山ラスト
（影山）う
（白布）く
This is our chance! Spike it again!
チャンスだもう１発たたけ
They made our setter receive it.
セタに取らせやがた
Ushijima!
（川西）牛島さん
Don't panic.
（東峰）焦るなタイミングを
外したら終わり
If our timing is off, it's all over.
（東峰）せの
Ready, and... jump!
Do I want a way to fight in spite of my short stature?
（鷲匠）俺は小さくても
戦えるすべが欲しいのか
違う俺は
No, I...
want a simple strength that can make anything surrender.
俺も—
すべてねじ伏せる
シンプルな強さが欲しい
（西谷）ぐ
（西谷）う
おお粘る
They're not giving up!
クソでもさきから
返すだけで精いぱいだ
Damn it! It's taking all they have just to get the ball back over the net!
A rally where both sides are low on stamina
and are fighting for momentum...
（一繋）残り少ない体力を懸けて
流れを取り合うラリ
Don't let your energy run out,
and don't stop hitting the ball.
ボルも気力も
切らすんじゃねえぞ
It hasn't hit the ground yet!
（東峰）まだ落ちてない
（田中･西谷）まだ落ちてない
Stop it!
This point!
（３人）この１点
（烏野一同）絶対取るんだ
We have to get it, no matter what!
Shut up! We're the better team!
（白布）うるせえ
こちのほうが強い
（ホイスル）
（白鳥沢一同･白鳥沢応援団）
よしゃ
All right!
Nice spike, Ushijima!
（応援団員）ナイスキ牛島
（日向）くうう
Ushijima!
（３人）ううう
One more point! One more point!
（白鳥沢応援団）あと１点
あと１点あと１点
Shiratorizawa                   Karasuno
This is bad. Everyone's mood just got dark.
（武田）
いけないみんなの空気が重い
But we don't have any more timeo—
でもタイムアウトはもう
（繋心）
下を向くんじゃねええええ
Don't you dare look down!
Volleyball...
バレは
常に上を向くスポツだ
is a sport where you're always looking up!
（谷地(やち)仁花(ひとか)）ハァハァハァ
Hitoka!
仁花ちゃんえ
（山口･日向）あ
（谷地の荒い息）
（谷地のせき込み）
A-Are you okay?
I'm not used to taking stairs two at a time...
（冴子）だ大丈夫
（谷地）普段階段の
２段飛びなどしないもので
All right!
Now that Yacchan's back,
it's finally time for the counterattack!
（嶋田）よしやちゃんも
帰てきたしいよいよ反撃だ
Episode Nine:
The Volleyball Idiots
Next time on Haikyuu!!:
"The Volleyball Idiots."
次回「ハイキュ」